Student Newspapers; Collection ua809
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- State College News, 1940s, 1940-1949; 4; 263 Digital Files
  - State College News, 1948, 24 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 10, 1948 December 3; 7.15 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 11, 1948 December 10; 6.37 MB
  - State College News, 1949, 24 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 12, 1949 January 7; 5.98 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 13, 1949 January 14; 7.07 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 14, 1949 February 11; 7.23 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 15, 1949 February 18; 7.29 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 16, 1949 February 25; 6.94 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 17, 1949 March 4; 5.73 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 18, 1949 March 18; 7.28 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 19, 1949 March 25; 7.00 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 20, 1949 April 1; 6.90 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 21, 1949 April 8; 6.92 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 22, 1949 April 29; 6.88 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 23, 1949 May 6; 7.15 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 24, 1949 May 7; 4.29 MB
    - State College News, Volume 33, Number 25, 1949 May 13; 5.84 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 1, 1949 September 23; 6.32 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 2, 1949 September 30; 6.94 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 3, 1949 October 7; 7.22 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 4, 1949 October 14; 5.15 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 5, 1949 October 21; 6.87 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 6, 1949 October 28; 7.11 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 7, 1949 November 4; 7.09 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 8, 1949 November 10; 7.11 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 9, 1949 November 18; 7.02 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 10, 1949 December 2; 7.03 MB
- State College News, 1950s, 1950-1959; 5; 258 Digital Files
  - State College News, 1950, 27 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 13, 1950 January 6; 6.30 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 14, 1950 January 13; 7.13 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 15, 1950 February 10; 5.29 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 16, 1950 February 17; 7.01 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 17, 1950 February 24; 6.65 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 18, 1950 March 3; 6.45 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 19, 1950 March 9; 7.04 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 20, 1950 March 17; 7.00 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 21, 1950 March 24; 7.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 22, 1950 April 14; 5.33 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 23, 1950 April 21; 7.02 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 24, 1950 April 28; 7.14 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 25, 1950 May 5; 6.95 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 26, 1950 May 6; 4.82 MB
    - State College News, Volume 34, Number 27, 1950 May 12; 6.03 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 1, 1950 September 22; 6.46 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 2, 1950 September 29; 7.34 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 3, 1950 October 6; 7.42 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 4, 1950 October 12; 5.49 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 5, 1950 October 20; 5.46 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 6, 1950 October 27; 7.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 7, 1950 November 3; 7.06 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 8, 1950 November 10; 7.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 9, 1950 November 17; 5.62 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 10, 1950 December 1; 7.52 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 11, 1950 December 8; 7.32 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 12, 1950 December 15; 6.55 MB
  - State College News, 1951, 25 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 13, 1951 January 5; 4.26 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 14, 1951 February 9; 6.86 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 15, 1951 February 16; 7.09 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 16, 1951 February 23; 7.15 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 17, 1951 March 2; 5.48 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 18, 1951 March 9; 7.01 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 19, 1951 March 16; 7.29 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 20, 1951 April 13; 7.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 21, 1951 April 20; 7.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 22, 1951 April 27; 5.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 23, 1951 May 4; 7.01 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 24, 1951 May 9; 4.97 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 25, 1951 May 11; 7.05 MB
    - State College News, Volume 35, Number 26, 1951 June 14; 4.30 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 1, 1951 September 21; 5.75 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 2, 1951 September 28; 6.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 3, 1951 October 5; 6.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 4, 1951 October 12; 5.20 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 5, 1951 October 19; 6.78 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 6, 1951 October 26; 7.05 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 7, 1951 November 2; 6.75 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 8, 1951 November 9; 7.02 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 9, 1951 November 30; 7.06 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 10, 1951 December 7; 6.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 11, 1951 December 14; 4.36 MB
  - State College News, 1952, 28 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 12, 1952 January 11; 5.60 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 13, 1952 February 6; 6.84 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 14, 1952 February 15; 6.75 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 15, 1952 February 22; 5.09 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 16, 1952 February 29; 7.00 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 17, 1952 March 7; 5.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 18, 1952 March 14; 6.79 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 19, 1952 March 21; 6.52 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 20, 1952 March 28; 6.46 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 21, 1952 April 4; 5.66 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 22, 1952 April 25; 6.59 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 23, 1952 May 2; 6.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 24, 1952 May 9; 6.58 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 25, 1952 May 10; 5.07 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 26, 1952 May 16; 6.79 MB
    - State College News, Volume 36, Number 27, 1952 June 11; 4.16 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 1, 1952 September 19; 6.54 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 2, 1952 September 26; 6.99 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 3, 1952 October 3; 7.11 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 4, 1952 October 10; 5.49 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 5, 1952 October 17; 7.24 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 6, 1952 October 24; 7.30 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 7, 1952 October 31; 7.18 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 8, 1952 November 7; 7.01 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 9, 1952 November 14; 7.26 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 10, 1952 November 21; 5.20 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 11, 1952 December 5; 7.22 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 12, 1952 December 12; 6.08 MB
  - State College News, 1953, 24 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 13, 1953 January 9; 6.00 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 14, 1953 February 6; 7.17 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 15, 1953 February 12; 7.35 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 16, 1953 February 20; 7.20 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 17, 1953 February 27; 7.51 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 18, 1953 March 6; 7.09 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 19, 1953 March 13; 9.13 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 20, 1953 March 20; 6.65 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 21, 1953 March 27; 7.32 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 22, 1953 April 17; 5.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 23, 1953 April 24; 7.25 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 24, 1953 May 1; 6.97 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 25, 1953 May 8; 4.86 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 26, 1953 May 9; 4.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 37, Number 27, 1953 May 15; 6.22 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 1, 1953 September 18; 6.24 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 2, 1953 September 25; 7.04 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 3, 1953 October 2; 6.91 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 4, 1953 October 9; 7.03 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 5, 1953 October 16; 7.28 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 8, 1953 November 6; 7.30 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 9, 1953 November 13; 7.03 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 10, 1953 December 4; 6.80 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 11, 1953 December 11; 5.99 MB
  - State College News, 1954, 26 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 12, 1954 January 8; 6.22 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 13, 1954 February 5; 6.99 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 14, 1954 February 12; 6.95 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 15, 1954 February 19; 5.43 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 16, 1954 February 26; 6.91 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 17, 1954 March 5; 6.79 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 18, 1954 March 12; 7.31 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 19, 1954 March 19; 7.04 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 20, 1954 March 26; 6.03 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 21, 1954 April 6; 5.19 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 22, 1954 April 9; 5.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 23, 1954 April 30; 7.37 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 24, 1954 May 7; 5.09 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 25, 1954 May 8; 5.01 MB
    - State College News, Volume 38, Number 26, 1954 May 14; 6.36 MB
    - State College News, Volume 39, Number 1, 1954 September 17; 6.32 MB
    - State College News, Volume 39, Number 2, 1954 September 24; 7.07 MB
    - State College News, Volume 39, Number 3, 1954 October 1; 6.97 MB
    - State College News, Volume 39, Number 4, 1954 October 6; 7.08 MB
    - State College News, Volume 39, Number 5, 1954 October 15; 7.13 MB
    - State College News, Volume 39, Number 6, 1954 October 22; 10.75 MB
    - State College News, Volume 39, Number 7, 1954 November 5; 6.86 MB
    - State College News, Volume 39, Number 8, 1954 November 12; 6.79 MB
    - State College News, Volume 39, Number 9, 1954 November 19; 5.25 MB
    - State College News, Volume 39, Number 10, 1954 December 3; 6.72 MB
    - State College News, volume 39, Number 11, 1954 December 10; 5.85 MB
  - State College News, 1955, 24 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 39, Number 13, 1955 January 7; 5.89 MB
    - State College News, Volume 39, Number 14, 1955 February 4; 7.07 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 3, 1955 February 18; 7.23 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 4, 1955 February 25; 7.07 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 5, 1955 March 4; 6.87 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 6, 1955 March 11; 6.89 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 7, 1955 March 18; 7.15 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 8, 1955 March 25; 7.30 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 9, 1955 April 22; 6.93 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 10, 1955 April 29; 7.27 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 11, 1955 May 6; 5.26 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 12, 1955 May 7; 4.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 13, 1955 May 13; 5.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 14, 1955 September 23; 4.60 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 15, 1955 September 30; 6.56 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 16, 1955 October 7; 6.72 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 17, 1955 October 14; 6.62 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 18, 1955 October 21; 6.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 19, 1955 October 28; 6.82 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 20, 1955 November 4; 6.82 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 21, 1955 November 11; 6.78 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 22, 1955 November 19; 4.95 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 23, 1955 December 2; 6.65 MB
    - State College News, Volume 40, Number 24, 1955 December 9; 9.09 MB
  - State College News, 1956, 26 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 25, 1956 January 6; 6.04 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 26, 1956 January 13; 6.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 1, 1956 February 10; 6.35 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 2, 1956 February 17; 5.58 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 3, 1956 February 24; 6.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 4, 1956 March 2; 5.77 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 5, 1956 March 9; 5.94 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 6, 1956 March 16; 5.21 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 7, 1956 March 22; 6.21 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 8, 1956 April 13; 5.92 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 9, 1956 April 20; 3.09 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 10, 1956 April 27; 7.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 11, 1956 May 4; 6.46 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 12, 1956 May 5; 4.65 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 13, 1956 May 11; 6.87 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 14, 1956 September 21; 5.46 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 15, 1956 October 5; 8.29 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 16, 1956 October 12; 6.45 MB
    - State College News, volume 41, Number 17, 1956 October 19; 8.16 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 18, 1956 October 26; 7.26 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 20, 1956 November 2; 5.84 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 21, 1956 November 9; 5.30 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 22, 1956 November 16; 5.92 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 23, 1956 November 30; 8.00 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 24, 1956 December 7; 7.74 MB
    - State College News, Volume 41, Number 25, 1956 December 14; 8.04 MB
  - State College News, 1957, 24 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 1, 1957 February 8; 6.19 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 2, 1957 February 15; 7.52 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 3, 1957 February 22; 6.41 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 4, 1957 March 1; 6.77 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 5, 1957 March 8; 6.55 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 6, 1957 March 15; 8.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 7, 1957 March 22; 6.30 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 8, 1957 March 29; 6.14 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 9, 1957 April 4; 6.16 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 10, 1957 April 26; 7.85 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 11, 1957 May 3; 6.21 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 12, 1957 May 4; 4.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 13, 1957 May 10; 6.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 14, 1957 September 20; 5.33 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 15, 1957 September 27; 6.30 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 16, 1957 October 4; 6.06 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 17, 1957 October 11; 7.34 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 18, 1957 October 16; 6.04 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 19, 1957 October 25; 5.95 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 20, 1957 November 1; 5.86 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 21, 1957 November 8; 5.27 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 22, 1957 November 15; 6.22 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 23, 1957 December 6; 6.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 42, Number 24, 1957 December 13; 5.64 MB
  - State College News, 1958, 28 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 25, 1958 January 10; 4.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 1, 1958 February 7; 7.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 2, 1958 February 14; 7.74 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 3, 1958 February 21; 5.98 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 4, 1958 February 22; 6.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 5, 1958 February 28; 5.64 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 6, 1958 March 7; 6.17 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 7, 1958 March 14; 8.85 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 8, 1958 March 15; 5.79 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 9, 1958 March 28; 6.09 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 10, 1958 April 19; 7.65 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 11, 1958 April 25; 6.16 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 12, 1958 May 2; 6.36 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 13, 1958 May 9; 7.62 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 14, 1958 May 23; 6.10 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 15, 1958 May 31; 2.57 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 16, 1958 September 19; 5.00 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 17, 1958 September 26; 5.86 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 18, 1958 October 3; 6.13 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 19, 1958 October 10; 5.88 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 20, 1958 October 17; 5.93 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 21, 1958 October 24; 7.45 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 22, 1958 October 31; 6.05 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 23, 1958 November 7; 6.08 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 24, 1958 November 14; 7.29 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 25, 1958 November 21; 5.88 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 26, 1958 December 5; 5.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 27, 1958 December 12; 7.21 MB
  - State College News, 1959, 26 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 43, Number 29, 1959 January 9; 6.05 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 1, 1959 February 6; 7.22 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 2, 1959 February 13; 7.25 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 3, 1959 February 20; 5.89 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 4, 1959 February 21; 2.65 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 5, 1959 February 27; 7.06 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 6, 1959 March 6; 5.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 7, 1959 March 12; 7.11 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 8, 1959 March 20; 5.71 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 9, 1959 April 10; 5.55 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 10, 1959 April 17; 5.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 11, 1959 April 24; 6.89 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 12, 1959 May 1; 6.88 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 13, 1959 May 5; 5.15 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 14, 1959 September 18; 4.92 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 15, 1959 September 25; 5.45 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 16, 1959 October 2; 5.99 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 17, 1959 October 9; 7.06 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 18, 1959 October 16; 7.05 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 19, 1959 October 23; 6.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 20, 1959 October 30; 5.70 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 21, 1959 November 6; 7.23 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 22, 1959 November 13; 7.03 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 23, 1959 November 20; 5.94 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 24, 1959 December 4; 5.73 MB
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 25, 1959 December 11; 5.68 MB
- State College News-State University News-Albany Student Press, 1960s, 1960-1969; 6; 337 Digital Files
  - State College News, 1960, 26 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 44, Number 27, 1960 January 8; 5.58 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 1, 1960 February 5; 5.51 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 2, 1960 February 12; 7.57 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 3, 1960 February 19; 6.17 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 4, 1960 February 20; 3.01 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 5, 1960 February 26; 5.05 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 6, 1960 March 4; 5.54 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 7, 1960 March 11; 6.00 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 8, 1960 March 16; 6.66 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 9, 1960 March 25; 3.16 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 10, 1960 April 1; 6.89 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 11, 1960 April 22; 6.02 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 12, 1960 April 29; 7.25 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 13, 1960 May 6; 5.69 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 14, 1960 May 13; 6.09 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 15, 1960 September 30; 6.86 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 16, 1960 October 7; 7.18 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 17, 1960 October 14; 6.03 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 18, 1960 October 21; 6.11 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 19, 1960 October 28; 6.21 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 20, 1960 November 4; 7.07 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 21, 1960 November 11; 7.38 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 22, 1960 November 18; 7.29 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 23, 1960 December 2; 5.88 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 24, 1960 December 9; 7.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 25, 1960 December 16; 6.12 MB
  - State College News, 1961, 27 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 28, 1961 January 6; 4.45 MB
    - State College News, Volume 45, Number 29, 1961 January 13; 5.84 MB
    - State College News, Volume 46, Number 1, 1961 February 10; 5.87 MB
    - State College News, Volume 46, Number 2, 1961 February 17; 7.21 MB
    - State College News, Volume 46, Number 3, 1961 February 24; 6.86 MB
    - State College News, Volume 46, Number 4, 1961 March 3; 5.48 MB
    - State College News, Volume 46, Number 5, 1961 March 10; 4.71 MB
    - State College News, Volume 46, Number 6, 1961 March 17; 6.27 MB
    - State College News, Volume 46, Number 7, 1961 March 21; 5.25 MB
    - State College News, Volume 46, Number 8, 1961 April 11; 4.19 MB